healia.com 2008-09-14

# Healia - health search engine

Awards:  

| 

Privacy Policy

Healia is completely committed to protecting your privacy. We realize that ensuring user privacy is particularly important for a health search engine. This privacy policy describes what information we collect on our site and how it is used. This policy only applies to our site. When you click on a link on a search result page, on an ad, or a sponsored message on our site, you will leave Healia and the privacy policy of the site you visit applies. You should review the privacy policies of all Web sites before you use them. We have no control over the content or the privacy practices of other Web sites. 

Our site collects information about users and site usage to better understand your needs and to improve our technology. We do not collect "personally identifiable information" about you unless you provide us that information voluntarily. Personally identifiable information is information that can be used to identify you as an individual, such as your name, mailing address, some email addresses, SSN, or telephone number. You do not have to provide any personally identifiable information to use this Web site. 

We will never disclose, give, sell, or transfer any personally identifiable information about visitors, unless required by law enforcement, a court action, or by statute. 

**Collected Information**

Information about users and site usage may be collected when you visit any Web site. Our Web server collects and stores the following information about each visit to help us improve our site: 

  * the name of the domain you use to access the Internet (e.g., aol.com, hotmail.com, harvard.edu) 
  * the date and time of your visit 
  * the pages you visited and any links, ads, or messages you accessed 
  * the address (URL) of the Web site you were previously at before accessing our site 
  * the search terms and any content filter options you submitted 
  * any email addresses submitted to us when sending links to others or when submitting feedback to us 

**Cookies**

Cookies are small bits of software code placed on your computer's hard drive by a Web site. This small file helps your Internet browser remember certain information so that the Web site can efficiently communicate with your browser. Our site can only read the cookies placed on your computer by us. We cannot access any information on your hard drive placed there by you or any other source. Our cookies cannot read your computer's files or harm your computer. Cookies are not traceable to an individual user. 

We may use cookies to track site usage. For example, they will allow us to determine what features people use when visiting our site and how long they stay there. We may use cookies for the following purposes: 1) to improve our search results and site navigation for users, 2) to provide users with more relevant ads or messages from our sponsors, and 3) to monitor how visitors use our site and select search results, ads, and sponsor messages. This information is used to improve our site and may be shared with sponsors. 

If you turn off cookies on your Internet browser, you can still use our site but you may have to reject a cookie each time you access our site. 

**IP Addresses**

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is associated with your computer each time you access the Internet. This is determined by your Internet Service Provider (ISP) and the address may or may not change each time. IP addresses are not associated with personally identifiable information. Like other Internet sites, we use IP addresses to collect summary information about users and site usage. This information is recorded by our Web servers. We may use the IP address to identify individuals who attempt to illegally compromise our site or disrupt service to our users. 

We may share anonymous, summary information about users with sponsors, advertisers, or other third parties. Such summary information cannot be used to identify an individual or to link an individual with a specific health condition. We may use summary data for statistical purposes.
